jobrapido.net 2013-12-06

# 

Tax code and VAT number: IT11876271005  
Company registered at the Chamber of Commerce of Milan  
Fully paid up share capital: € 5.000.000  
us@jobrapido.com

2\. Data collected during navigation  
When you visit the Jobrapido Website, it collects certain Personal Data, such as the pages you view, the links or buttons that you click, the date and time when you access the Site, your IP address, your web browser and the operating system you use (the "Navigation Data").

The Navigation Data may, by its very nature, allow Users to be identified through processing and association with data held by third parties. However, Jobrapido uses this data solely for the purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information concerning the use of the Site and for purposes strictly related to its operation.

The Jobrapido Cookie  
When you visit the Site for the first time, Jobrapido saves a Cookie on your browser (identified as JE). This is a text string consisting of a code stored on your computer. This code allows Jobrapido to recognize your browser, to automatically identify you through your registered email and to display information connected with your interests. The Cookie is permanent and if not renewed will disappear after a period of 2 years. If you wish to delete the Cookie before this period, you can do so at any time using your browser settings.

The Cookie will be placed on your computer only if this option is enabled on your browser. Some features of the Site may not work correctly if this option is disabled.

Third party cookies  
Jobrapido uses third party services that install Cookies. These third party services are:  
•Google Analytics, provided by Google Inc, which installs the Cookies "__utma", "__utmb" and similar. For more information: developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies  
•Google Adsense, provided by Google Inc, using the DoubleClick Cookie. For more information: www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ads/#toc-doubleclick  
If you wish to receive further information about third party Cookies, please write to our email address.

Other Navigation Data  
When you open a new Job Ad notification email or click on a link it contains, your action is tracked for statistical purposes.  
3\. Data provided voluntarily  
Your email address  
Jobrapido allows you to activate a notification system for new Job Ads (Job Alert). Users can activate the notifications using their email address, geographical area and/or the kind of job they would like to see Ads for.

After your email address has been provided, the Data is used only to send an initial email that is just an example of the Job Alert Service, and a second email as a reminder. Actual registration with the Job Alert Service only takes place upon acceptance of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service by clicking on one of the links contained in the email.  
The email address is stored for the period and the purposes strictly necessary to request consent, and the Job Alert Service will not begin unless one of the links is clicked.

You can enter the email address manually or you can identify yourself through the social network Facebook authentication service provided by Facebook Inc. Facebook authentication allows access to some basic information on your profile and information related to the permission you give when you authorize our application. Jobrapido, however, only uses your email address and does not record any other information, except in so far as is strictly necessary to make the integration work.

When you click on the links in the messages sent to your email address, Jobrapido uses its Cookie to identify you on later visits, allowing you to change the search parameters you are monitoring and for which you are notified by email. If you don't want to be identified on the next visit, you can click on the "log out" link.

In addition to notifications for new listings, Jobrapido can send you specific job offers. These offers come from our partners who are interested in the professional profiles you are monitoring. Jobrapido will use the email address you provided solely and exclusively for the Job Alert Service. Jobrapido will not send any business or advertising mail of its own or from any third party to the address you give without your consent.

When you cancel the Job Alert notifications, the Service will be discontinued and your address will be removed from our database. The Service may also be stopped and your email may be removed from the database in other circumstances, e.g., when you stop clicking on the Job Alert links.

Users are free to give their own email address to receive the Job Alert Service. Failure to provide it, however, will make it impossible to obtain the requested Service.

Other Personal Data provided voluntarily  
As part of the Services offered by the Site, you may provide Jobrapido with other Personal Data besides your email address in order to receive more information and Services (such as requesting information, quotes, subscribing to Services offered by the Site, replying to an ad, reporting malfunctions etc.).  
This data will be processed by Jobrapido solely for purposes strictly related to your request. We are not responsible of any use of the data by employers or any third party advertiser who may access your information on this Site. Failure to provide this information may make it impossible to obtain the requested service.

Ad reply form  
This form allows you to contact the Job Advertiser directly, and also to attach your Curriculum Vitae. Jobrapido does not store any of the Personal Data provided in this way and only carries out the minimum processing of data necessary in order to send the Advertisers the information provided.

Job Advertisers  
This part of the Site allows businesses to request information on the Services Jobrapido offers for companies, such as posting Job Ads on the Site. The Personal Data provided will be used for offers relating to the Services mentioned, both through direct contact or by sending occasional email messages.

Uploading your Curriculum Vitae onto the Evenbase Group's database to share it with recruiters  
Jobrapido lets you upload your Curriculum Vitae onto the Evenbase Group’s database, making it and the Personal Data contained in your Curriculum Vitae available to recruiters who have subscribed to receive such information by email and/or to search for candidates in the Evenbase Group database using various search criteria (“Curriculum Services”). Curriculum Services are provided by the Evenbase Group and are subject to their legal terms and privacy policy (see www.evenbase.com for more information). You can amend, substitute your Curriculum Vitae or request that Curriculum Services are discontinued at any time.  
4\. Third party services  
Jobrapido uses third party services for its statistics, for technical management and maintenance or to display advertisements on its Site. The list of services used, and thus the third parties, varies greatly depending on the national locations of the Site, making it technically impossible to list them in this document. We therefore suggest you contact us if you wish to receive complete information.

Other third party services  
Jobrapido makes use of a number of partners to show ads related to Jobrapido on third party websites and to allow partner advertising networks to display ads that take into account User preferences. These ads can take into account the fact that the User is registered with Jobrapido or has visited the Site. Recognition by these partners is by means of a Cookie and by sharing the Jobrapido Cookie, described above, with them. No other Data is shared with these partners.  
Partners offering this service are Criteo (run by Criteo SA, privacy policy and opt out on www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy) and Simpli.fi (run by Simplifi Holdings, Inc., privacy policy on www.simpli.fi/ad-serving-privacy-policy/ and opt out on app.simpli.fi/opt_out).  
5\. Personal Data Processing procedure  
We handle your data in accordance with legal requirements, taking all appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, unauthorized modification or destruction of Personal Data. The Data is processed using both manual methods and computers and/or telematic means, using organizational and logical methods strictly related to the stated purposes.

Subject to your express consent, we may supply Personal Data about you to selected third parties so that they may contact you with information and offers which may be of interest to you.  
Jobrapido reserves the right to disclose your Personal Data to comply with applicable laws and government or regulatory bodies’ lawful requests for information.  
Jobrapido may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or business reorganisation.  
6\. Place of Data processing  
The Personal Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, but the services offered by Evenbase Group, Google or other partners, may be processed outside Italy and/or outside the European Union.  
7\. Data retention  
Personal data is processed for the time needed to perform the requested services and is deleted by Jobrapido when the purpose for which it was collected and processed no longer exists.  
8\. User rights  
You may contact Jobrapido at the contact addresses given, to obtain:  
i. confirmation of the existence or otherwise of Personal Data regarding you and, if it is stored, the list of Personal Data in Jobrapido's possession  
ii. information on the terms and purposes of the processing of your Personal Data  
iii. updating or modification of your Personal Data  
iv. cancellation of your Personal Data, including the deactivation of the Job Alert service and/or Curriculum Services.

9\. Changes to these Terms  
Jobrapido reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, informing Users through the Site.  
Users who continue to use the Service after the publication of the new conditions accept the new Privacy Policy in its entirety.  
10\. Legal information  
This privacy policy is subject to the laws of Italy.  
11\. Definitions  
Ad or Job Ad  
A job advert accessible through the Site, whose content is published directly on Jobrapido or retrieved automatically from other job ad sites, as indicated in the ad itself, and of which Jobrapido publishes an extract.

Advertiser  
Those who publish Job Ads through the Jobrapido website.

Service  
The service of indexing, publication, and displaying Ads on the Site and any communications via email provided by Jobrapido.

Terms of Service or Terms  
These general terms of service.

Personal Data  
Personal data is any information concerning a natural person, identified or identifiable, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

Interested party  
The person or entity to whom the Personal Data refer.

Website or Site  
Jobrapido, a search engine for jobs that operates through local versions in various countries of the world, identified by the jobrapido.com website.

Data Controller  
The natural person, legal person, public administration and any other organization or association with the right, also jointly with another owner, to make the decisions regarding the purposes and methods of processing of personal data and the means used, including the security profile, in relation to the operation and use of this Site.

User  
The individual user of the services or products of the Site.
